mlm-thewholetruth.com 2007-12-20

# MLM-theWholeTruth.com - Privacy Policy

Use of www.MLM-theWholeTruth.com is subject to the Terms and Conditions (the "Terms and Conditions"), all other policies, and to this privacy policy (the "Privacy Policy"). www.MLM-theWholeTruth.com respects and protects the privacy of individuals in accordance with generally accepted principals contained.  

## CONSENT

This statement discloses the privacy policy and practices of www.MLM-theWholeTruth.com and of www.MLM-theWholeTruth.com. By using www.MLM-theWholeTruth.com or by agreeing to the Terms and Conditions you consent and agree, without limitation or qualification, to the collection, use and disclosure of personal information and to the privacy practices set out in the Privacy Policy and to any other privacy or data collection policy which is displayed or is included as a link at www.MLM-theWholeTruth.com. 

##   
USAGE OF INFORMATION

Information provided by the customer through www.MLM-theWholeTruth.com will only be used to enhance and improve the customer experience at www.MLM-theWholeTruth.com and will never be sold, rented or distributed. www.MLM-theWholeTruth.com may share personal, individual information with certain partners to facilitate the provision of services to our customers. 

This Website, www.MLM-theWholeTruth.com partners with other trusted companies for processing of accounts and customer orders. This Website, www.MLM-theWholeTruth.com has asked that any processing undertaken by such companies adhere to data protection principals. Contact information such as customer and user e-mail addresses, phone numbers, shipping/billing addresses and credit card information, is needed to complete your transaction. Information that www.MLM-theWholeTruth.com collects is stored in a secure manner with restricted access. 

##   
UPDATES

All changes will be posted on www.MLM-theWholeTruth.com promptly to inform visitors and customers of what information is collected, how it is used, and under what circumstances it may be disclosed. Customers are advised to review this Privacy Policy occasionally for any updates. 

##   
DISCLAIMER AND CONTACT

www.MLM-theWholeTruth.com shall not be responsible or liable for any loss of privacy, disclosure or information, harm, damage or loss that may result from your transmission or any information to us in any connection with www.MLM-theWholeTruth.com. www.MLM-theWholeTruth.com will cooperate fully with any law institution should a situation arise where our information can be of assistance. If you have any further questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please e-mail us.
